http://www.ultravision.co.uk/privacy-policy

EVENTS ABOUT
Group BoardInnovation & LicensingAwardsQuality Certificates PATIENT
Changing Lives
Patient VideosKevin MacNeil's StoryGareth Smith's Story Keratoconus
What is Keratoconus?KeraSoft and CXLKeratoconus FAQsVision Problems?Over 40?Patient Lens Care PROFESSIONAL
PracticesHospitals Keratoconus
Refitting from RGPsKeraSoft and CXLCase StudiesFitting KeraSoft IC Conferences
GSLS 2017 MoRoCCo App
MoRoCCo VA App SupportAvanti Prescription ConverterContact Lens Fitting Tool Lens Care
SiH Lens RemovalBenz 3x Material LensesOpaque Tinted LensesSolutions & CleanersPatient Information LeafletNew Account Registration PRODUCTS
Silicone Hydrogel
AvantiHydroWaveAphakic & MyopicBandagePaediatric Soft Hydrogel
IGEL ProDuraWaveSAM MF SOFTOther Products Keratoconus & Irregular Corneas
KeraSoft ThinKeraSoft ICKeraSoft3 & KeraSoft2ALK & McGuireXtralens Hospital
Cosmetic & TintsAphakic & MyopicBandagePaediatricSpecialist Bandage Gas Permeable
TopflexEurekaALK & McGuireSAM MF RGP Disposables
SEED Daily DisposablesUltraWaveSpecialty 55 ABCosmetic & TintsTerms & ConditionsORDER CONTACT
Key ContactsClinical SupportEnquiry FormHOME NEWS
EVENTS ABOUT
Group BoardInnovation & LicensingAwardsQuality Certificates PATIENT
Changing Lives
›
Patient VideosKevin MacNeil's StoryGareth Smith's Story Keratoconus
›
What is Keratoconus?KeraSoft and CXLKeratoconus FAQsVision Problems?Over 40?Patient Lens Care PROFESSIONAL
PracticesHospitals Keratoconus
›
Refitting from RGPsKeraSoft and CXLCase StudiesFitting KeraSoft IC Conferences
›
GSLS 2017 MoRoCCo App
›
MoRoCCo VA App SupportAvanti Prescription ConverterContact Lens Fitting Tool Lens Care
›
SiH Lens RemovalBenz 3x Material LensesOpaque Tinted LensesSolutions & CleanersPatient Information LeafletNew Account Registration PRODUCTS
Silicone Hydrogel
›
AvantiHydroWaveAphakic & MyopicBandagePaediatric Soft Hydrogel
›
IGEL ProDuraWaveSAM MF SOFTOther Products Keratoconus & Irregular Corneas
›
KeraSoft ThinKeraSoft ICKeraSoft3 & KeraSoft2ALK & McGuireXtralens Hospital
›
Cosmetic & TintsAphakic & MyopicBandagePaediatricSpecialist Bandage Gas Permeable
›
TopflexEurekaALK & McGuireSAM MF RGP Disposables
›
SEED Daily DisposablesUltraWaveSpecialty 55 ABCosmetic & TintsTerms & ConditionsORDER CONTACT
Key ContactsClinical SupportEnquiry Form
PRIVACY POLICY
UltraVision CLPL is committed to protecting your privacy when you access and use our ultravision.co.uk web site (the “Site”) and provides you this notice that any data or information collected and used by UltraVision CLPL in connection with the Site and services or materials available or enabled via the Site (“Services” and “Materials”) are governed by this online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) as amended from time to time, and not any privacy in effect at the time the data and information was collected. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with any other web site (including any web sites linked to), offline activities or other products, services or materials not available or enabled by this Site.
1. CHANGES IN PRIVACY POLICY
Any information that identifies or can be used to identify the person to whom such information pertains (“personal information”) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time.
UltraVision CLPL may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in its sole discretion and will provide notice of changes in the Privacy Policy and on the Site’s home page. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and Services and Materials. Unless at the time you provide personal information to UltraVision CLPL you expressly limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by UltraVision CLPL or third parties,
UltraVision CLPL will not change your preferences in this regard without your consent, and you will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to the changes to the Privacy Policy after UltraVision CLPL has posted the notice of changes in the Privacy Policy and on the Site’s home page.
2. PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES
You have the right at all times to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences. Any Registration Information may be edited or corrected by you once you are logged in by clicking “Update Your Profile” on the Site, or you can edit and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing to UltraVision CLPL at:
UltraVision CLPL
Commerce Way,
Leighton Buzzard,
Bedfordshire,
LU7 4RW
UNITED KINGDOM
UltraVision CLPL is committed to respecting your preferences and legal rights with respect to access to, correction of, and deletion of your personal information. Except in particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, or where required by law, regulation, litigation, national security or law enforcement, UltraVision CLPL will not provide your name to other companies or organisations without your consent.
If you provide UltraVision CLPL with inconsistent privacy preferences (e.g. indicating on one occasion that you may be contacted with respect to marketing offers from UltraVision CLPL or third parties and on another that you may not be contacted with respect to such offers) UltraVision CLPL will update its records with your latest preference in a timely and accurate manner.
UltraVision CLPL is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any non-UltraVision CLPL web sites to which this Site, the Services or any Material may link. You are strongly advised to review the privacy policy(ies) of any of these sites before using them.
UltraVision CLPL also adheres to European Union Safe harbor principles and retention of personal information covered by the Privacy Policy from the European Union.
3. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
As you access and use the Site, Services and Materials, UltraVision CLPL may from time to time ask you to provide certain information and data about yourself by filling out and submitting a form or a field on the Site. This information could include for example your first and last name, mailing address, country of residence, e-mail address, telephone or facsimile number, work address and other information. Of course, it is optional for you to provide such information, however, in some instances
UltraVision CLPL may require certain mandatory information about you in order for you to gain access to or use the Site, the Services and Materials. If you do not provide mandatory data and information with respect to that particular access to or use of the Site, the Services or Materials, you will not be able to access or use the Site, the Services or Materials. Or, if you wish to delete your data and information (as provided in Section 2 above) and such data or information is mandatory, then you may no longer be able to access or use the Site, the Services or the Materials.
In order to facilitate our evaluation of your use of the Site, the Services and the Materials, UltraVision CLPL will also from time to time collect information about your computer which may include among other information, its operating system, CPU speed, Internet Protocol (IP) address, referring or exit web pages and browser type. UltraVision CLPL will use this information to measure your use of the Site, the Services and Materials to support, evaluate, enhance and supplement your user experience with the Site, the Services and Materials. We may also match or link this information with any other information held by UltraVision CLPL.
Cookies, web beacons and similar tracking devices
UltraVision CLPL may use cookies, web beacons or other devices to track your use of the Site, the Services or the Materials (e.g. types of Services or Materials used, number of uses or downloads, number of users of the Site, the Services or the Materials) and our web servers will automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any use individually.
UltraVision CLPL may use this aggregated information for improving and enhancing the Site, the Services and Materials and for statistical analysis. It is not UltraVision CLPL’s practice to use this information for any other purposes or to identify any user personally, however, where you have expressly provided consent for the Site, the Services or the Materials to “remember” the unique identifier that you select when you register your account, that unique identifier will be stored on a cookie on your computer and that unique identifier will be linked to your Registration Information.
For your information and understanding, a cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It serves as your ID card and enables the web server that gave it to you to record your passwords and preferences.
A web beacon is a small gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. Similar devices can be embedded in the Services or Materials to send data to a web server when a set of user-initiated events occur, as when a user clicks on one or more buttons to initiate an action, direction or response on the Site.
Most browsers default to allow or accept cookies, and most products and services that include similar devices also default to activate or allow the collection of data. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it (however, some web pages, including those that may be contained in web sites linked to this Site, may require an authorization and may not grant you the option of choosing not to accept cookies or similar devices and will likely not allow you to access those pages or any related products or services).
You are also advised that some products and services, including some of the Services and Materials on this Site may allow document authors to restrict access to documents, track access to or use of those documents, or involve transmission of data over the Internet to verify authenticity of authors, recipients and documents. Where this type of tracking is not obvious to you, the software and/or services license or terms of use, pop-ups or notifying e-mail will inform you of these features and of any options available to you to disable the features.
4. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
UltraVision CLPL collects your personal information to support, record, facilitate and enhance your use of the Site, the Services and the Materials. When you register an account for the Site, the Services and/or the Materials, the information is logged to register your rights to tech support and other benefits made available from time to time to registered users.
Except where prohibited by law or where you have opted to not receive such communications, we also use your personal information to track your use and preferences and to keep you informed about product and service upgrades, and other products and services of UltraVision CLPL, its partner vendors and partner service providers and other third parties.
5. PROTECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
UltraVision CLPL classifies the personal information that you submit and provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the Site, the Services or the Materials as “Registration Information.” Your Registration Information is protected in the following ways:
(a) Access by you to your Registration Information is available only through a password and unique user identifier select by you and the password is encrypted. (UltraVision CLPL strongly advises that you not share your password or unique customer ID to anyone.)
(b) Your Registration Information resides on secure servers that only selected UltraVision CLPL personnel and contractors have access to via password. These personnel and contractors are bound under strict confidentiality agreements with UltraVision CLPL prohibiting disclosure or use of your Registration Information other than for its intended purposes as contemplated by this Privacy Policy.
© UltraVision CLPL encrypts your personal information as it is transferred to UltraVision CLPL’s secure servers thereby taking reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized parties for viewing, disclosing or using such information.
Any personal information that you submit or provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on UltraVision CLPL’s secure servers and is accessible only by selected UltraVision CLPL personnel and contractors have access to via password. These personnel and contractors are bound under strict confidentiality agreements with UltraVision CLPL prohibiting disclosure or use of your Registration Information other than for its intended purposes as contemplated by this Privacy Policy. This information is not accessible to you online and so you will not be required to select a password in order to view or modify it.
6. TRANSFERS OF INFORMATION TO SUCCESSORS AND ASSIGNS
You acknowledge and agree that if UltraVision CLPL sells or assigns assets (or the assets of any division or subsidiary) to another entity, or UltraVision CLPL (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with another entity, UltraVision CLPL may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to, assigned to, or merged with the other entity without obtaining your further consent, but UltraVision CLPL will provide notice of such asset sales, assignments, acquisitions, or mergers on the Site.
7. COMPLAINTS
If you feel that UltraVision CLPL has failed to comply with its obligations under this Privacy Policy or otherwise have complaints with respect to UltraVision CLPL’s use or protection of your personal information, you may fill out a Privacy Complaint form and send it to UltraVision CLPL’s Privacy Officer at the following address:
UltraVision CLPL
Commerce Way,
Leighton Buzzard,
Bedfordshire,
LU7 4RW
UNITED KINGDOM
Please be specific in your complaint and provide as much detail as possible so that we can promptly address your concerns. We will investigate and respond to all complaints promptly.
